[{"answer": "Some weather we're having.  Must be from all the meshugass at that place.  You locked out of your apartment", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Good night, Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "That's me.", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I should have stayed in bed last night", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "That's right, my friend", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "What kind of joint are you running", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Oh", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "No, sir. I'm not going to deny it. But if you'd just let me explain", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "You know how people talk", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Not that I have anything to hide", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I'm sorry, but I can't tonight. I'm meeting somebody", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No. Like a man", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Eigh", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "All right? That's wonderful! It's the Majestic", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Do I. That leaky little boat you rented", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "We talked about a lot of things", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I mean", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You didn't really believe me, did you", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " Just trust me, baby", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I wasn't trying", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Of course not", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Much better", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Not so rough, honey", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Good night", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Doctor", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "It's a thought", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "See if they'll what", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Oh", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " my friend", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Something wrong with your legs", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Your stomach", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Three across, spades double, high deals.  Eight", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Give what up", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Why not", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": " I don't like myself very much anyway", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Hi, my friend", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "What do I", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "What gives", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Go where", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I guess so", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "A what", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "I see.  What do you think, my friend? Can we help the man", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Yeah. What's Budd", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I don't", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "What for", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Why did you take sleeping pills", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": " Sir", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": " You're going to take her off my hands", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "That's very wise", "docId": "Apartment_-The.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Good night, my friend", "qsentId": 52}]